{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Bauer_(officer)",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1895-11-24",
    "human_readable": "Michael Bauer was born on November 24, 1895.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8885760307312012,
            "question": "Is November the month in which Michael Bauer was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8717547059059143,
            "question": "When was Michael Bauer born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8063075542449951,
            "question": "What is the significance of November 24th for Michael Bauer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7477720379829407,
            "question": "Was Michael Bauer born before 1900?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7353262901306152,
            "question": "What is Michael Bauer's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6441497802734375,
            "question": "What month and day was Michael Bauer born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309806704521179,
            "question": "Is Michael Bauer's birthdate in the 19th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.620391309261322,
            "question": "Can you tell me a fact about Michael Bauer's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47738003730773926,
            "question": "In what year did Michael Bauer come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4707188010215759,
            "question": "How old would Michael Bauer be today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Bauer was born on November 24, 1895.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2485_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Michael Bauer come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2485_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me a fact about Michael Bauer's birthdate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2485_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michael Bauer's birthdate in the 19th century?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2485_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2485_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query \"Michael Bauer was born on November 24, 1895\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple documents mentioning Michael Bauer, and one of them (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2485/re-ranker-msmarco/99.txt) mentions his birth year as 1973, not 1895."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nExplanation: The document `85.txt` contains the information about Michael Bauer, including his date of birth as \"24 November 1895,\" which supports the statement that he was born on November 24, 1895."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are multiple individuals with the name \"Michael Bauer\" mentioned in the context information, born in different years (1895, 1973, and others), making it likely that the specific birthdate of November 24, 1895 is associated with one of them, not necessarily Michael Bauer.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}